

Full Stack Web Developer

+233504628244 eddiedanqz11@gmail.com B470/11, Nii Awuley Lartey street,Accra Ghana linkedin.com/in/edmund-danquah/

PROFILE

I am a self-motivated full-stack web developer with 5 years of experience in website design and development. Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development. Ability to adapt to self-starting and collaborative environments. I am comfortable with technologies like Vue.js, Laravel and as well as other technologies for web development. Excited to pursue new companies to learn and grow my skills.

SKILLS

Web Languages

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MYSQL

Frameworks

- React.js
- Vue.is
- Laravel
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS

Other Technologies

- Firebase
- Heroku
- Git
- Wordpress

EXPERIENCE

011/2021 - Present

Full-Stack Web-Developer, Quality Services Ltd

- Participate in the design of and creation of dynamic, visually attractive web apps.
- Worked with a team and developed web apps for clients.
- Integrated social media tools and SDK into website.

Technologies: Laravel, React, Relational Database, Heroku, Git

04/2021-07/2021

Freelance Web-Developer, Startimes Ghana | Airport City, Accra

- Built a desktop application to track customer service agent's performance.
- Helped with gathering information for the implementation of requested features. This included interviewing the employees who would be using the application the most.

Technologies: Vue, Electron.js, SQL, Git

06/2017 - 11/2018

Front-End Web-Developer, Signet Global | Accra,

- Worked as a frontend developer and designed the company's entire webpresence.
- Recommended web design features for the company.
- Maintained all the software resources and ensured that they were always working properly.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Relational Database,

EDUCATION

Graduated - 2018 **Diploma in Information Technology**, Ghana Technology University | Accra, Ghana